<Strings>

  <String Name="MoveControlMode.Pad">触摸板</String>
  <String Name="MoveControlMode.Buttons">按钮</String>
  <String Name="LookControlMode.Pad">仅触摸板</String>
  <String Name="LookControlMode.EntireScreen">全屏幕</String>
  <String Name="LookControlMode.SplitTouch">分离 触控</String>

  <String Name="GameMode.Creative.Description">创造模式中，你拥有无限供应量的物品而且你能以无限快的速度挖掘方块。你还拥有不死和飞行的能力。</String>
  <String Name="GameMode.Harmless.Description">无害模式中，所有的危险因素都会被移除。动物不会主动攻击你，除非你招惹它们。从高处跌落变得不那么致命。健康值得回复速度很快。挖掘速度提高 25%。</String>
  <String Name="GameMode.Challenging.Description">挑战模式是正常生存模式。你会遇到危险，但当你死亡时，你可以在你上一次睡觉的地方复活。</String>
  <String Name="GameMode.Cruel.Description">残酷模式与挑战模式相同，但你不能复活。明智地进行游戏，因为一旦你死了，你就再也不能回到你的世界了！</String>
  <String Name="GameMode.Adventure.Description">冒险模式是专为那些想要创造探索性的地图，并与其他玩家分享的玩家准备的。在这种模式中，你只能使用专用的工具挖掘方块，你的健康值不会自动回复。在创造模式中创建探索性地图，然后在上传之前切换成冒险模式。</String>

  <String Name="EnvironmentBehaviorMode.Living.Description">In Living mode the world is a living place full of animals. Plants and grass grow, blocks made of loose material collapse and detached leaves decay.</String>
  <String Name="EnvironmentBehaviorMode.Static.Description">In Static mode the world has no animals. Plants growth, block collapsing and plant decay are disabled. Useful if you want to shape your world the way you want it.</String>

  <String Name="TimeOfDayMode.Changing.Description">Time of day will change periodically. Sun, moon and stars will move across the sky.</String>
  <String Name="TimeOfDayMode.Day.Description">Time of day will always be noon. Sun, moon and stars will stay stationary in the sky.</String>
  <String Name="TimeOfDayMode.Night.Description">Time of day will always be midnight. Sun, moon and stars will stay stationary in the sky.</String>
  <String Name="TimeOfDayMode.Sunrise.Description">Time of day will always be morning. Sun, moon and stars will stay stationary in the sky.</String>
  <String Name="TimeOfDayMode.Sunset.Description">Time of day will always be evening. Sun, moon and stars will stay stationary in the sky.</String>

  <String Name="TerrainGenerationMode.Normal.Description">在正常模式中，环境就像真实世界的一样，充满了森林、平原、沙漠、冰川、湖泊、山脉、丘陵、山洞 ……</String>
  <String Name="TerrainGenerationMode.Flat.Description">在平坦模式中，地形完全是平的，给你最大程度的创作自由。你可以自由改变地形的高度以及组成地形的方块。</String>

  <String Name="FlatTerrainLevel.Description">调整平坦模式中地形相对于基岩的高度。这个值越低，地上空间越多。这个值越高，地下空间越多。</String>
  <String Name="FlatTerrainMagmaOcean.Description">将海洋变成岩浆之海。</String>
  <String Name="TemperatureOffset.Description">调整此世界的全局温度。</String>
  <String Name="HumidityOffset.Description">调整此世界的全局湿度。</String>

  <String Name="WeatherMode.True">此世界会发生周期性的降雨和降雪，降雪后会形成积雪。闪电会击中高处的物体，并使其着火。</String>
  <String Name="WeatherMode.False">没有降雨、降雪、闪电。</String>

  <String Name="AdventureRespawnMode.True">玩家可以在他上一次睡觉的地方或者出生点复活(适合大型的、有检查点的冒险地图)。</String>
  <String Name="AdventureRespawnMode.False">不允许复活，当玩家死亡时，只能重新开始。(适合大型的、没有检查点的冒险地图)。</String>

  <String Name="AdventureSurvivalMechanics.True">饥饿值、体力值、体温、睡眠需求度 在冒险模式中起作用。</String>
  <String Name="AdventureSurvivalMechanics.False">饥饿值、体力值、体温、睡眠需求度 在冒险模式中被禁用。健康值仍然起作用，玩家仍会受到伤害。</String>

  <String Name="CharacterSkin.Description">选择游戏中角色的皮肤。</String>
  <String Name="BlocksTexture.Description">选择用来绘制世界的方块纹理。通过选择不同的方块纹理，你可以彻底地改变世界的面貌。</String>

  <String Name="ExternalContentType.BlocksTexture">方块纹理</String>
  <String Name="ExternalContentType.World">世界</String>

  <String Name="Settings.Compatibility.InvisibleModelsWorkaround.Description">Enable this if you cannot see animals in the game. It selects a slower, less optimized code path which runs correctly on a wide range of devices even with a buggy shaders implementation.</String>
  <String Name="Settings.Compatibility.SinglethreadedTerrainUpdate.Description">Enable this to force the game to use a single thread only when updating the terrain. It will make the game run slower on multicore devices, but might make it slightly faster on single core ones.</String>
  <String Name="Settings.Compatibility.UseAudioTrackCaching.Description">Enable this if you experience issues with audio and have Android 4.3 or earlier. This setting reduces the number of AudioTrack objects created.</String>
  <String Name="Settings.Compatibility.UseReducedZRange.Description">Enable this if you experience issues with graphics like invisible parts of the world near the player or garbled textures. It reduces the clip-space Z range from -1/1 to 0/1, as some Android devices have depth buffering and clipping issues with the full range.</String>
  
</Strings>
